Pi Beta Phi Sorority, NY Delta Chapter Records.
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Pi Beta Phi records, 2002.
37-4-3271
Pi Beta Phi.New York Delta Chapter (Cornell University)
2.1 cubic ft.
Scrapbooks
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Architectural drawings and abstract of title, history and pledge class scrapbooks. Also chapter bylaws, 2002.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Architectural drawings and abstract of title, history and pledge class scrapbooks. Also chapter bylaws, 2002.
SUBJECTS
Names:
Pi Beta Phi.; Cornell University--Societies, etc.
Subjects:
Greek letter societies.; Women--Societies, etc.; Women college students--New York (State)--Ithaca.
Form and Genre Terms:
Scrapbooks.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
CONTAINER LIST
- Pi Beta Phi Sorority History and Pledge Class Scrapbooks
  - Chapter By-laws, 2002 (Box 1)
  - Abstract of Title for house, 1989 (Box 1)
  - Chapter History scrapbook and account of chapter history, 1919-1934 (Box 2)
  - Wooden covers of 1951-1952 scrapbook (Box 2)
  - Fabric cover of 1974-1975 scrapbook (Box 2)
  - Fabric cover of 1980-1981 scrapbook (Box 2)
  - Painted plastic cover of 1983 scrapbook (Box 2)
  - Fabric cover of spring 1991 scrapbook (Box 2)
  - (Chapter history) Petition to the Pi Beta Phi Fraternity from Pi Beta Phi Fraternity, 1919 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Pi Beta Phi Chapter History, 1934 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Chapter History, 1936-1937 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - History of New York Delta Chapter of Pi Beta Phi (in original order #1-123), Sept. 1951- Feb. 1952 (Box 3, Folder 4-6)
  - Scrapbook (in original order), 1958 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Cover from 1958 scrapbook (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Pi Beta Phi scrapbook (in original order #140-252), 1963 (Box 4, Folder 1-3)
  - Cornell News (clippings), 1966-1967 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Pi Beta Phi, Delta Chapter scrapbook, 1974-1975 (Box 4, Folder 5-6)
  - Pi Beta Phi scrapbook, Fall 1975 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Pi Beta Phi scrapbook, 1979-1981 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Pi Beta Phi scrapbook, 1980-1981 (Box 5, Folder 1-2)
  - Pi Beta Phi scrapbook, 1983 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Pi Beta Phi scrapbook, 1985 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Pi Beta Phi scrapbook, 1990 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Pi Beta Phi scrapbook, 1992 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Pi Beta Phi scrapbook, 1962 (Box 6)
  - Pi Beta Phi scrapbook, 1992 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Pi Beta Phi scrapbook, 1997 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Pi Beta Phi scrapbook, 1998 (Box 7, Folder 3-4)
  - Pi Beta Phi scrapbook, 2001 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Active Member Directory, ca. 2000s (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - New Member Facebook and Manual, 2006 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Celebrating 75 Years of Sisterhood (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Pi Beta Phi scrapbook, 1963 (Box 8)
  - Class composites, 1953, 1954, 1956 (Box 8)
  - Kappa Kappa Gamma and Pu Beta Phi photograph, 1955 (Box 8)
  - Pledge formal photograph, 1955 (Box 8)
  - Building plans (Folder 1)